Filtering the data to include only the observations you need,
过滤数据使数据仅包括你需要的观察结果
can dramatically improve query speed.
能够大幅提高查询速度
How you do this will depend entirely on the problem you're trying to solve.
如何执行这一操作将完全取决于你要试图解决的问题
For example, if you've got time series data,
例如 如果你获得了时间序列数据
limiting to a small time window can make your queries run much more quickly.
限定一个小时间窗口能大大提升你的查询速度
Keep in mind that you can always perform exploratory analysis on a subset of data.
记住 你时刻都能够用数据子集进行探索性分析
Refine your work into a final query,
执行最后的查询以完善你的作品
then remove the limitation and run your work across the entire data set.
然后移除限制并在整个数据集上运行你的作品
The final query might take a long time to run,
最后的查询可能会花费较长时间
but at least you can run the intermediate steps quickly.
但至少你能够快速运行中间步骤
This is why most SQL editors automatically append a limit to most SQL queries.
这也是为什么大多数 SQL 编辑器自动为大多数 SQL 查询设置限制的原因
They expect that for exploration,
他们希望对于探索性分析
a limited result set is fine.
能够获得有限结果
Once you have a final query,
一旦你运行了最后查询
you can turn off the limit and get the full results.
你可以取消限制并得到全部结果
It's worth noting that limit doesn't quite work the same way with aggregations.
需要注意的是限制与聚合的运行原理并不完全一样
The aggregation is performed first,
首先进行的是聚合
then the results are limited to the specified number of rows.
然后结果被限定到具体的列数
So, if you're aggregating into one row,
因此 如果你加总到一列
limit 10 will do nothing to speed up your query.
但限定 10 这将无助于提高查询速度
Again, if your results is more than 10 rows,
另外 如果你的结果超过 10 列
this will limit it down at only the last step.
只能在最后一步设置限制
So the most expensive parts of the query,
因此 查询最费力的部分
the aggregations will be performed first.
是首先运行聚合
Then, the result set will be limited,
然后 结果将被限制
which won't save you that much time.
但这节省不了你多少时间
If you want to limit the data set before
如果你打算在运行计数前先限定数据集
performing the count to speed things up a little more,
以便能更好的提高查询速度
you'll need to do it in a sub query.
你需要运行子查询
In general, when working with sub queries,
一般而言 使用子查询时
you should make sure to limit the amount of data you're working
你应该确保在数据运行的地方
with in the place where it will be executed first,
限制你处理的数据量
in order for it to have maximum impact on a query runtime.
以便能够最大限度地影响查询运行时间
This means usually putting limit in the sub query not the outer query.
这意味着一般需要在子查询而不是外部查询中设定限制
Keep in mind, that applying a limit to a sub query will dramatically alter your results.
牢记一点 使用子查询将很大程度上改变你的结果
So, you should use it to test query logic but not to get actual results.
因此 你应该使用子查询测试查询逻辑而不是获得实际结果
As you can see, the results from this query
正如你看到的 这一查询的结果
are much different than when we used the limit in the outer query.
与我们在外部查询中设定限制获得的结果非常不同